Hello, welcome to Market Sense
Tamil. I am your Rahul.  Today in this
video, we are going to discuss in great detail what the
top 5 health insurance
products are in the Indian health insurance market in 2026
.  So,
how do we optimize these products? Let's first
look at some performance metrics.  The claim
settlement ratio is
the number of hospital beds in the claim ratio
.  And also compatible
volume.  That means we check the complaint volume to
check what kind of service they are providing to the customer
.  So, we make decisions based on this
and also take a close look at the
futures of the important product
.  So, we have compiled this
list of top 5 health insurance
products based on that.
Surely some companies have come up with better
performance metrics than this one
.  But when I
looked at its products, I avoided it from this particular list because it lacked up-to-date,
competitive product features
.
That is the main reason for it.  So
in this video, we'll discuss the completeness of it and go into
detail about what the premiums are like with the last one
.  And we'll see what kind of
products come out and who will be
suitable for them
.  So definitely skip it,
you'll enjoy it
.  Purchase life health insurance
.  We are opening a demat account,
so please feel free to contact us and
get services from me.  We will provide 100% after-
purchase and claim assistance, all support
from our side
.  I have a good team.   Those who
already purchase from me
know this very well.  Let's
go into the video now.  If this is
your first time
visiting my channel, please subscribe to my channel and click the bell icon as I post useful content related to stock
market, personal finance and
insurance
.  So that when I upload a video, I
get a notification.  If you liked this video, please like it
.
Don't forget to comment with your thoughts.
Don't forget to hype it up.  If any of your friends
and family are researching to
purchase life insurance or health insurance,
please share this video with them
.  You will have Yusufullah
.  Let's go into the video now
.  Let's take a look at
what the performance metrics of First Company look like
.  So, the
top 5 companies I've listed here are not just
based on performance
metrics.  So,
I've seen their product features since it arrived
.  That means that some companies have
come along and performed better than the performance metrics I have given here
.  But
we avoid them because the features in that company's product are not competitive with the data
.  It doesn't make it into this top 5.  So,
we put them on this list based on the product's quality, not just the performance metrics
.  The first thing
we look at here is the claim
settlement ratio.  So, for those who don't know what this claim
settlement ratio is,
I'll
repeat it once.  If 100 complaints are
received, how many of them
are settled? For example,
100 claims are received.  If a 98
claim is settled, then that
company's claim settlement ratio
is 98.
How many hospitals
are there in the Diabetic community that are not network hospitals? They will come and
say that they are network hospitals.  This type of
diabetes can be treated directly at hospitals, where you can come and
get your treatment without having to pay cash, just give your card.  If you
don't come and type it, then you will have to come and
pay from your own pocket and
then submit these documents and get
reimbursed
.  So this is the
advantage of this network hospital.   If the
complaint volume is like that and
10,000 claims are coming in, how many
complaints are coming in and
being registered with Insurance Humbertsman?
That's how this complaint
volume is. I always
give a lot of importance to the complaint volume.  Because
this complaint volume is so high,
not everyone will just come and complain to the ombudsman.  Only those from the upper middle class
and those who know the law well would
go for such things.  So, when
it comes to that value,
I will definitely
give it more importance.  As far as the Inker claim ratio is concerned, if
you collect over Rs 100 crore in
premium in a year,
how much will you settle when you get a claim back?  For
example, if you settled a claim of Rs. 80 crore,
we can say that the company's Incourt Claim Ratio is 80.  So let me tell you the importance of this claim
settlement ratio and the increase in claim
ratio for our business
.  What some companies
do is have an extraordinary claim settlement
ratio of
98%.  But
their income claim ratio
will not be up to date and up to mark.
What's the reason for that? If so,
they will settle for a higher amount if the policy comes with a lower claim
.  So, they must have settled
for a higher number of policies
.  Their claim
ratio will be high.  But a
single policy will cost 2 crores or 3 crores, something like that
.
There is a chance that your unclaimed claim ratio will be full because all the policies that are similar have not been settled.
So when you look at the overall performance of a company, you don't
just look at our claim segment ratio, but also our in-claim
ratio. Overall,
you
get an understanding of how a company is performing overall.  So now, for the
value we've taken, we've
taken a 3-year average claim settlement rate.  Let's
go to the network hospital and get our medicine
.  The complaint volume has
arrived and is up to date.  Regarding the Incur Claim
Ratio,
we have taken the data provided by Lasta as the Incur Ratio for the 2024-25 financial year.
This is the updated data
for these features.  Now, regarding these
performance metrics,
HDFC
Erbo Optima Secure came first, came in at 96.7, and the
claim ratio of network hospitals
came in at
13,000 plus network hospitals
.
In terms of complaint volume,
seven complaints
are registered for every 10,000 customers.  They are giving an Incurred Claim Ratio of
84.85.  So, we are giving you this product,
HDFCO Optima Secure, which ranks first among us
.  The second thing we're going to see is
a product like the Active 1 Max from Adi Birla.  So, this is what
happened with that company, and your claim
ratio is 95.81.  Network
hospitals are coming in, and 12,000-plus
hospitals are coming in and are on the waiting list.   The
complaint volume has reached 18.677,
with 10,000 complaints
being registered.  This
is a little high,
and the Incurred Claim Ratio is
71.50, which is a
decent Incurred Claim Ratio.
As for Care Supreme, their claim
set ratio is 93.13.
This is the third one on our list
.  And
as for network hospitals, there are 11,400 plus network
hospitals.  The complaint
volume has increased to 36 complaints and
10,000 claims have been registered.  So,
this is definitely
something we should pay close attention to.  If
you look at my claims, many
people's claims are getting delayed, and
we can all experience that with Care Supreme.
And as for the Incurred Claim Ratio,
they have an Incurred Claim Ratio of 64.53%
.  This is not too bad.
They should definitely improvise.
They have a decent unsecured claim ratio
.  And fourth on our
list is the Niva Bhupala, where
we have taken the Rio 2.0 Platinum variant
.  So, from here, the
claim ratio of this company is
91.62.  The number of people who are in the
hospital type with them comes to 10,000
plus hospitals and complaint
volume comes to 43 out of 10,000
claims, 43 complaints come and
are registered, 10,000 claims,
they should definitely come and improve.  This is also a delay in
providing our services.
I have never received rejection from my clients
.  Delice is definitely
coming.  As for Yuva Buppa.
And their
Incurred Claim Ratio is 61.22, so there
is definitely room for improvement.  Butt isn't too
bad.
They have given a decent income ratio.
And don't worry, our company is
coming and Iic Lombard.
The product arrived and was delivered to Lampard Elevate.
So, they come here and give us a claim ratio of 84.56
.  So this is
definitely a poor claim
segment ratio, comparatively speaking, but
in terms of other metrics, i.e., the
listed hospitals' complaint
volume is coming up, 11 complaints
are being registered out of 10 claims
and also the unclaimed claim ratio is coming up,
80-82.24%
.  So, this is what I got and I think
they're
doing a good job with the metrics.  But
we clearly know that there is definitely room for them to improve that claim ratio
.  But why did I choose this product? When
I
looked at the overall performance of this company, how they settle claims, their digital presence, all this, I thought that this
product and also this product
futures could
give me the top spot
.
I have given my claims to many people.  There has
been no rejection so far.  Your
claim is also coming along and going a little smoother,
but that's my personal opinion
.  And now let's take a look at the
features of this product one by one. First of all,
in terms of coverage limit, HDFC
Optima Secure can cover you from Rs.
5 lakhs to Rs. 2 crores
.   If you
come to the office and take care of 5 lakhs to 2
crores,
you can take care of Supreema from 5 lakhs to 1 crore
.  This can also be taken
from 5 lags to 1 core
.  ICICI Bank has
come to Elevate and you can come and get cover ranging from Rs. 5 lakhs to Rs. 3
crores
.  Regarding minimum and maximum age for
entry,
you must be at least 18 years old to join HDFC
.  There is no limit once the maximum is reached
.
You can get this policy at any age.  But the
underwriting team will come and design it based on the medical condition that exists at that time
.
For dependent children, you can also apply for
this policy 91 days before the child is born
.  If you failed to do so, you can
come back and complete one year and then
do it again during the renewal period.  Once you have a child, you can continue to have
this particular policy until the child turns 25, and then
you
can renew it.  Once
you have children and are over 25 years old,
they will switch to an adult individual policy.
And as for the principal, if
you are an adult and want to enter the policy, you
must be 18 years old.  There is no limit once the maximum is reached
.  You should come to the same different
child from 0 to 19 days and
before 91 days.
And also, if you have a
child and this policy is renewed, and
you come and see a child,
you can continue this policy until the age of 30
.  As for Care Supreme,
you must be 18 years old to be eligible for
this policy, with no minimum or maximum limit.
For dependent children, the same should be done from
0 to 91 days.  Once
you have come and entered,
you can continue this policy with your child until they are 25 years old.
You can only enter Niva Bhoopal if you are over 18 years of age
.  The maximum has been reached and the
limit has been reached here.  There is no
limit yet.  They
came here after reaching the age of 65 and have reached the maximum limit
.
As for Pree Shore.  You can add dependent children to
your account 0 to 91 days
before they arrive.  If you
missed this,
you can do so when you renew.
Once you apply, your child will
come and be covered by the policy you have, and
now your child will come and be covered by
this particular policy until the age of 30
.  That's within the policy.
For ICICI Lombard and
Elevate, you
can apply for this policy only after you have reached the minimum age of 18 years.  Maximum 125 years.  These 125
years are unlimited.
That's what they're saying indirectly.  Child,
you can have a policy for 0 to 91
days. After you come and make your first entry,
your
child can come and renew it until they turn 30 and continue with the same
policy.   So
this is it until the age limit comes
.  And this policy gives
you a lot of unique selling
points over individual products
.  They are telling
you that you will get 2X benefit as far as HDFC ERBO is concerned
.  Then,
the amount of cover you take will
be doubled immediately.
For example, if you buy a policy for 10 lakh
rupees, you will get a policy as soon as you buy it.
In that case, as soon as you buy the policy, they will
immediately give you another 10 lakh rupees
.  You can carry forward that 10
lakh rupees until next year
.  You can renew it for the second year, but
you can still come back and carry it forward
.  It's
an important thing to remember that you can't carry forward anything after that.
Something to note.  And R.
As far as Abirla is concerned, they have come up with things
like super reload and super credit and
have created unique selling points.   When we
see it in full, we can discuss it in great detail
.
As for AndK Supreme, they come to you and
give you an optional cover like Cumulative Bonus Super.  So this has become
a unique selling point
.  So what is this cumulative bonus? If so,
our
normal policy comes and we claim or
not,
our sum measure will increase
.  So, they come and
say it's a bonus.  So, if
you subscribe to this rider in this
particular policy,
then you will get
100% every year. For example, if you have a
shortfall of 10 lakh rupees, the
next year
you renew it, whether you make a claim or
not, you will get
another 10 lakhs. So, this
type of maximum goes up to 100% and 500%
.  That means if you come and
have a cover of 10 lakh rupees,
then it will almost certainly increase
until it reaches 60 lakh rupees and
you get more cover
.  So,
you
have a unique selling point for this Care Supreme.
As for Nivappa, you
have a selling point for a uni that is like Lock the Clock Future.  This lock the clock is like that and
you take out a policy.
For
example, you
take out a policy at the age of 25.
In terms of health insurance, the premium for health insurance increases according to the age
bracket, meaning your age also increases accordingly
.  But since
you
have this locked-in future, your premium will not change for this particular policy
until you make your first claim
.  If you take out a policy at the age of 25,
you won't go to the clinic until you're 50, so your
premium will remain the same.  Sometimes
there are small inflation-adjusted changes, but
your premiums
will not increase as you age.  So this is
an
important unit selling point in this particular policy
and also they come and give
some options like booster plus and reor plus
.  So, when we come to our details and
look at the futures, we
can see that.  And
for ICICI Bank, they are also offering
this option called Infinite Care
.  This Infinite
is like an extra rider, you
can juice it up.  How
does this work? If you take a policy,
you
can use unlimited cover for any amount during the life of your policy. For example,
you take a cover of 10 lakh rupees
.  But I
renewed for 10 years and then a
big bill came, it came to one crore for a
single admission. So you come and
it comes to one crore in total and the company comes and
pays.
They will make a pot of water.  So this is an option that
you can use.
For Eliveta, this is definitely a
unit selling point.
And for road ambulances, they
come to you and give you some
insurance on Optima Secure
.  As for Adi Birla,
they are giving you a brief summary.
There is a slight limit on Care Supreme.  That is, if you
come and invest your sum of money for 15 lakhs,
then they
come to you and
give you a limit of 10,000.  And
this is what happens when you come and buy more than 10 lakh rupees,
more than 15 lakhs, and you buy some
insurance, and then you buy some insurance, and
you can
come and buy some
insurance, and you can use the
road ambulance for as much as you have
.  For Niva,
Nivapa, Rio 2.0, Up Sum
Insha Number Delivery,
Up Sum Insha
and Air Ambulance,
you get a
maximum from HFC and they give
you a limit of up to Rs 5 lakh, but
Aditya Birla comes and
you don't have air ambulance cover.   So
this is something you should take note of
.  And as for Care Suprema, they will
come and give you power for up to 5 lakh rupees per year
.  But this comes as an option and
not as an inbuilt feature.  It's
like you're paying extra for a premium
.  So you need to make a note of that.
And for Niwaba Rishore 2.0,
they come and provide you with an air ambulance, which costs you 2.5 lakhs for hospitalization
.  And
for the IC Nambadu elevator,
you also
have an air ambulance.  There is up to some
insurance.  But it came and was an extra
rider.  You will make Rider sauce.  Now
comes Room Rent Limit, IC Limit,
Domiciliary, Day Treatment, Modern
Treatments and Robotic
Surgeries.  So, in this regard,
you will get all these five products and
some insurance
will come and cover you.  But there
is only one exception to this.  IIC
Lambard comes in the elevator and
gives you a single private room with a maximum room rent limit.  So
this is not an AC room.  Single private
room.  So, this particular
product comes with a draw back.
But they come here and give you a rider,
like a room modifier, and if
you activate that rider, you
activate that rider and come and cover this
particular limit, single private room, and
you can
take any room you want and you
can even have it overwritten.  So, come and
keep that in mind.  Accordingly, IC
limit
is taking home treatment, day care
treatment, modern treatments,
all of which are available and can be used by some individuals
.  And for those who don't know,
I'll tell you what a domino is.  In that
case, we can't admit you to the hospital
.  You can get treatment at home,
the doctor recommends.
Why don't you stay at home and have a regular
doctor come and treat you?
So, in that kind of situation,
you can submit the bill and
get reimbursed.  So that's the
treatment in those domains.
That too comes up with some insurance.
As far as the no claim bonus is concerned, we are
fine.  So, as far as this no-claim bonus is
concerned, they will come to you
now and
give you the bonus whether you claim it or not.  So that's
why this no claim bonus is like that. They
only
give you the bonus for the years you haven't claimed before. And in case you claim a bonus
even after you've taken the bonus,
your bonus and
that bonus will be reduced by the same rate at which the bonus was increased in that year.  So that problem has
come up.
Modern politics is not like that here.   They will
give it to you whether you claim it or not.
As for HDFC,
whether
you claim or not, they will give
you a 50% bonus every year
.  If it comes to a maximum of
100%, and you have taken a cover of 10 lakh rupees,
the maximum it comes to
can go up to 20 lakhs.
As for Aditya Birla,
they will give you a 100% bonus whether you claim it or not.
The maximum can go up to 500%.
And as for Care Suprema, they will
come to you and
give you 50% annually, whether you claim or not.  If you take a maximum 100%
cut of 10 lakh rupees,
it will go up to 20 lakhs.
As for Niva Bupava,
you will get a bonus whether you claim it or not, even if you reach Platinum.  That bonus
comes 5x times.  How come we said 500 times,
500%, the same way if you
take a cover of 10 lakh rupees,
you will get a bonus as if you were covered by over 60 lakhs
.  And
as for the ICICI Lambard elevator, it's
a bit of a letdown when compared to this one.
They only give a 20% bonus when they come here
.  That too, will
only give you a 20% bonus if you don't make any claims during the claim-free year
.  It may reach its maximum and
reach 100% for you
.  So that option comes and
is in this particular policy.
So, regarding this localization bonus,
Elevate is
doing it like a competitor, a refill and recharge
option. So what is this refill and recharge option? So, when the
window comes,
you come and take a policy and
say base cover, you recharge
10 lakh rupees. That is what it
says base cover. You are
hospitalized and discharged.
So, how much base
cover you spent, they come and
refill it. Okay, so, they come and refill it partially or fully. For example,
you are admitted and you
empty the entire base cover of 10 lakh rupees, because it comes and is
discharged, it
is fully refilled.  When it comes, you fully recover, fully recover, and
when you are hospitalized,
you spend a small portion.  For
example, if you spend ₹3 lakh instead of ₹10 lakh,
then
when you are discharged, that ₹3 lakh
will be refunded.  That's when the
partial rep arrived.  So now, every
company has to come up with all the products and we have to
strictly fill this partially and fully
.
And when this amount of money comes in and
you are admitted, it should
cover the same disease as well as different
diseases.  What would some companies
do if they were to
give partial full compensation like this?  But if you are admitted
twice for the same disease in the same year, when
you are admitted for the second time, the
amount that was refunded will come and you will
not be able to use the cover.  So you can
check that.  So, in this particular
policy, we have given
you everything, partially, fully, fully, fully,
fully,
and also,
we have given you the same disease and different diseases, both covered.
This option is available on Optima Secure,
but only annually.  And
Aditya Parlal has this option.  It
comes and they give it unlimited time
.  And Care Supreme also
has this option.
They give it unlimited time.  It's in Realoral 2.0 and
they give it unlimited.  ic
is also in the Lampard Elevate.  They
come and give it unlimited.
As for Opadya, it is inbuilt in HFC,
but it has short limits.
Defense on ten insureds is
in the bag, so you can
buy an extra rider for that.  Care Supreme
does not have it. You do
not have it in the Platinum variant of Nivap Ratio 2.0.   I'm
coming to the Lombard Elevate and getting
treatment.  But for that you have
to take an extra rider.  For both,
only insurance and accident will come and
all policies will cover you.
So, for example, if there was an accident and the
doctor came and
made a recommendation at that time, in that kind of
situation, they would come and
cover your dental treatment.  But
without that, if you come and go directly to a
hospital and have a tooth cleaned
or a root canal done, then
you won't get this cover.
HDFC Bank also
offers 60 and 180 days for pre and post hospitalization.  Birla is
giving 90 and 180 days.  Care
Supreme comes with 60 and 180 days and
gives you 60 and 180 days, ICI Lambad Elevate comes with 90 and 180 days.
For consumers, HDFC has come and gone
.
You are getting an injection, Aythya.  If you
come to Care Supreme and
have an extra rider, you can buy PrideClaim Shield for that rider and then
you
can buy whatever you want.  And you should take the same extra cover when the ratio reaches 2.0
.  They say that's what the Claim Safe Card Plus is
.  So when
you do that, you
get cover and the consupils get cover too
.  As for ICICI Lambert, it would be
like you're getting an extra rider
.  It came with a clean protector
.  And as for the mattress, it's
optional for you, so you
can take it with you if you need it.   There
is no such thing as a hybrid.  Care is not supreme.
The ratio is not 2.0.  But I'll
come to you at ICICI Lambard.
You get 10%, you get sum insured,
you get material cover, you get it
.  Even for annual health care,
you have optimal
security, but
there is a minimum limit for that.  Even Birlalu has a
limit.  Care is at the Supreme,
you can make rider sauce.  There is a limit on Niva Booppan
.
As for ICICI Lambadi Elevator,
you haven't received your annual health check
.  As for riders, you can come and get
different and useful
riders for every individual product.  So, this is where
our main focus comes in. For HDFC Ego,
they are offering unlimited restore ABCD riders.  So we've already seen that
unlimited restore is not something we've seen in this
particular policy
.  The annual ones come and go, and the full ones
come.
We saw that some sort of insert came in and said that you can use the same table or different tables.  So, no matter
how many times you want to use it, it
will be repaid in a year.  If
you have this unlimited restore, ABCD rider,
etc., and you have an existing disease
like asthma, blood pressure, cholesterol, diabetes,
then they will generally impose a three-year
waiting period.  So, if
the three-year waiting period comes and you do it immediately,
that is, within 30 days,
then you can come and do this sauce
.  And
as for Aayitha Abrala, if
you come to us with a pre-existing disease and
you already have some
disease, then that disease will generally
impose a three-year waiting period,
but if you come to us with a two-year waiting period, you can
make it a one-year waiting period.  There is a rider for that
.  And
they say there is a specific waiting period.  They will give
you a two-year
waiting period for slow-growing diseases.  Then
you can come and make a profit for one year
.
They came and gave me a rider, saying it was chronic care
.  So, if they come and tell you that
you have hypertension and diabetes, and
you have this list of diseases, they will come and
give you cover from day one.  So, that's why
this rider comes and is used.  And
for Hair Supreme,
they also provide instant cover.  Sam, if you come and see me for the
hypertension, diabetes,
heart disease, and asthma you mentioned, you
can pretend that you'll get cover for 30 days.  And if you
have a pre-existing disease, the three-year
waiting period
can be reduced by one or two years.  There
's a rider for that here too.  And for the Niwaba Rio
2.0, there is a rider for one year coverage if you have a pre-existing
disease
.  You
can make any sauce you want.  And
as for Elevate, we've already seen this room
remodeler, haven't we?
As far as the room is concerned, they
only offer single private rooms.  If
the driver of this room gives you a lift, you
can book any room you want.   The
maternity waiting period comes,
the general one comes, and this particular
product comes and they put a two-year waiting
period on it.  You
can come and make a profit in a year.  And also
there is a rider from Gem Start.  So, you
came here and listed hypertension,
diabetes, and hyperthyroidism, and
gave me this list of diseases,
didn't you?  So, you can pretend that you get cover for all those diseases
after 31 days
.  So from
this, we see that
these riders are useful and important, and
I see that incase
consumables are
not included, so
you
can take extra consumables when you need them.  So that's an
important thing to come.  And also, if you come and
have a specific illness or an already existing disease, then they
come and
give you all the things you need to reduce it.
And what I find very unique about this is that they
generally give a two-year wait for specific slow-growing disease
.  Every
company has a problem, and you,
Aditya Prasad, can change it in a year
.
You can do it in one year. For example, if you come and see this appendix, this
appendectomy,
varicose veins, all this,
kidney stones, slow-
growing disease, all this, it will
definitely be two years before it happens.  So,
these guys came and got a
rider to make a profit for a year.  That's a
bit interesting.  But if
you look at the overall picture, existing
diseases are the main ones.  There are riders who come and go, there is a
waiting period, and then they
come to Sardine Disease and get a discount
.  Those who need it
can take Yusufullah.  So, overall, when you
look at all the features of this product and compare them,
you will see that
although there are some shortcomings, they are products that perform well and have
good features
.  So, if you
want a policy with a wholesome maternity policy,
you can definitely come and try ICICI Lambard
Elevated.
And a well-performing
company should provide you with
extraordinary customer care and a good claims experience
.   If
you are willing to pay a small extra premium for that, then you can
go for HDFC Atma Secure.
No, there must be a good company
.  Those futures must also
exist.  No need for metrics.
Premium should be a little more decent,
so you can go for Adi Barla.
There must be extraordinary futures.   If
you want a company that has attractive features and also an average performance, then you should
definitely consider Care Supreme or Nibaro
2.0. You can also consider these two products
.  So these are my
suggestions.  Now let's take a look at what this company's
premiums are like
.  I have written two examples, such as when this
comes and Kamana comes and all
the products come and cover 1 million rupees
.  An example comes up: the husband is
33 years old, and the wife is 29
years old.  The kid came and was a 3 year
old like that.  The second
example is when the husband comes and becomes 63
years old.  Vibe is 58 years
old.  I think that means it's a little
older
.  So
let's see what our premium looks like one by one.  As for HDFC Optima Secure, the first
example comes in at 2268 and the
premium comes in at 2268.  Second
example, if you call 77320,
you will receive a premium.  For Adi
Birla Active Active Max, the first
example
comes in at 1554 and the annual premium is 1554.   The
second exam comes with 46,143
.  And
for the Supreme Court, if you get 13.11 in the first exam and 48,396 in the
second exam,
you will get 48,396
.  And Nivapa Bupa Rio 2.0 here is
a Platinum, for the
first example
you get ₹1,722, and for
the second example you
get ₹45,527.  As for the IC Elambat Elevate, the
first exam
came in at 14,760
.  The second exam came, and
I  So when
I came to take this premium, I saw that
consumers should definitely be covered for all this particular product
.
Even for the IC number elevator, they
only came and gave me a single private room
.  I came to that particular place and signed up as a
room modification rider, so I
got that quote.  And we do not advertise our products in
any maternity products.  So this is
coming at a premium
.  So, I'm sure you'll find it useful to come and judge for yourself
what these examples look like to you
.
I hope you will enjoy this video.  If
you found this video useful
, please like it
.  Make it high.
Tell us your thoughts in the comments.
If your friends and family are
researching health insurance,
share this video with them too
.  So that they have the
opportunity to be useful.